

Ho Wing Law / Mickey

Product Designer

As a Human Computer Interaction student with 3 year product design experience, I have always been keen to perceive the needs and wants of users and create solutions to solve real world problems. I am a fluent speaker in English, Cantonese and Mandarin.

www.mickeylaw.design linkedin.com/in/mickeyhwlaw/ lawhw.design@gmail.com +44 7561 762486

Skills / Tools

Design

User Research
Design Ethnography
Product Design
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Information Visualisation

Graphic

XD, Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

Programming

Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, D3, R

Hardware / 3D

RaspberryPi, Rhino 3D, Solidworks, Keyshot

Education

MSc Human Computer Interaction

University of Nottingham, UK

2019 - 2020

BA (Honours) in Product Design

Technological and Higher Education Institute of Hong Kong First Class Honour, GPA:3.6/4 2012 - 2016

Experience

Product Designer II

VTech Telecommunications, Hong Kong

Designed in-house telecommunication products for AT&T, Snom and VTech. / Communicated and worked with project management team to follow up mass production.

Oct 2016 - Aug 2019

Research Project Assistant Internship

Hong Kong Design Centre, Hong Kong

Researched for influential designs and thoroughly analysed relevant information. / Evaluated potential designs in terms of their strong points, influence in Asia and commercial success.

Nov 2013 - Mar 2014

Volunteering / Leadership

Design Society Volunteer

Design Society (co-founded with London's V&A), Shenzhen, China Assisted the operations of events, such as design festivals, artists' and designers' talks. / Interacted with museum visitors and enhanced their visiting experience.

Oct 2018 - Sep 2019

Executive Committee Member - Secretary

Design Student's Society, THEi's Student Union, Hong Kong

Collaborated with Engineering Student's Society to organise orientation camp. / Helped arrange sponsorship from organisations. / Recorded minutes at meetings.

2012 - 2013

Awards

A' Design Award Runner-Up 2019

THEi Dean's List & President's List 2012-2016

Certification

IDEO Design Kit: The Course for Human-centered Design

Successfully came up with a healthy diet app concept with teammates and designed user flow and user interface.

Mar 2018